The scene with which we are going to start today's video is going to leave us indifferent. It belongs to
la escena con la que vamos a empezar el vídeo de hoy nos va a dejar indiferente pertenece a
the series Dad by Dan Sneider. You already know that Dan Sneider is a producer-director who is talked about
la serie al Dad de dan sneider ya sabéis que dan sneider es un director productor del que se habla
a lot. You also have a series on this channel. By the way. shadow of doubt that there is behind
mucho también tenéis una serie también en este canal Por cierta sombra de la duda que hay detrás
him with shady things and it is precisely in this scene in which we bring together Dan neider with
de él con cosas turbias y es que Precisamente en esta escena en la que juntamos a Dan neider con
pidid he wanted to have him for this somewhat strange cameo considering that this is a series for
pidid quiso contar con él para este cameo un tanto raro teniendo en cuenta que esto es una serie para
teenagers that of In fact, they are teenagers who shoot for children in this scene where we see
adolescentes que de hecho son adolescentes que tiran para pequeños en esta escena donde vemos
Didi surrounded by a bunch of kids, trying to wake up a child by throwing a white liquid
a Didi rodeado de un montón de chavales intenta despertar a un niño tirándole un líquido blanco
in his face and then when the kids come up to ask him for advice, for some reason he asks him
en la cara y luego cuando los chavales se acercan a pedirle consejo pididi por algún motivo le pide
to leave. I put a remote-controlled helicopter inside my pants and turn it on, I don't know, maybe
que se meta un helicóptero teledirigido dentro de los pantalones y lo encienda que no sé a lo mejor
I don't understand the language, maybe there's a type of sarcasm here or something like that that I can't
no entiendo el idioma y a lo mejor Aquí existe un tipo de Sarcasmo o algo por el estilo que no
quite get, but I think that taking into account everything I know is being shuffled today and everything
termino de pillar pero creo que teniendo en cuenta todo lo que se está barajando a día de hoy y todo
we have on the table danang sneider more pididi this looks a little strange no family
lo que tenemos sobre la mesa danang sneider más pididi esto queda un poco raro no familia
What are we Going To Do I don't know you know in situations like this yeah I Always
What are we Going To Do I don't know you know in situations like this yeah I Always
ask Myself What would p did do Oh What would p did do No I don't know Hey let's ask him
ask Myself What would p did do Oh What would p did do No I don't know Hey let's ask him
Okay we can't wake up sh you try syms yep What about sour Milk
Okay we can't wake up sh you try syms yep What about sour Milk
didn't work Tell you What Take this Toy helicopter put It Down all right
didn't work Tell you What Take this Toy helicopter put It Down all right
do didn't work He's Still
do didn't work He's Still
asleep try this
asleep try this
the contact of underage kids with some famous adults is a topic that we already
el contacto de chavales menores de edad con algunos famosos adultos es un tema que ya
covered in depth in the series that I already have on the channel about dagan neer, for example Jamie
tratamos en profundidad en la serie que ya tengo en el canal sobre dagan neer por ejemplo Jamie
ling Spear, Brit's sister spe surprised us all when we learned of her participation in some
ling Spear la hermana de brit spe nos sorprendió a todos cuando supimos de su participación en alguna
shady series of the elite although not of Peace Dad and that she was pregnant according to her by her boyfriend
serie turbia de la élite aunque no de paz Dad y que estuvo embarazada según ella de su novio
at 15 years of age while she was filming a series on Nickelodeon For more than one person is
a los 15 aos años de edad mientras que rodaba una serie en Nickelodeon Por más que una persona sea
famous to have certain shady conversations with minors is just as bad Even if the minor
famosa tener ciertas conversaciones turbias con menores es igual de malo Aunque el menor
is also famous What's up with my youth I'm Javi Oliveira welcome one more day to the Channel in this
también sea famoso Qué pasa mi chavalería Soy Javi oliveira bienvenidos un día más al Canal en este
specific video We are going to go into depth into a series of contacts let's say you have had Didi
vídeo en concreto Vamos a entrar en profundidad a una serie de contacto digamos que ha tenido Didi
or Didi's environment with minors also relating to everything that is being played and their
o el entorno de Didi con menores relacionándose también con todo lo que se está jugando y sus
famous parties and some even with supposed participation or well now we will see, you know
famosas fiestas y algunas incluso con supuestas participaciones o bueno ahora veremos ya sabéis
that this video is a second part of another that I uploaded yesterday So I recommend you that you
que este vídeo es una segunda parte parte de otro que subí ayer Así que os recomiendo que os
go to the channel first and watch the previous videos If you haven't seen them yet but
paséis por el canal primero y veáis los vídeos anteriores Si no los habéis visto todavía pero
this also belongs to a complete playlist where I am uploading
Igualmente esto pertenece a una lista de reproducción completa donde estoy subiendo
everything covering the Pat Dad case and we already have enough videos so that you are well documented
todo cubriendo el caso de pat Dad y ya tenemos bastantes vídeos para que estéis bien documentado
on the subject I also tell you that I will continue covering the story and any news that comes out I will be
del tema además os digo que seguiré cubriendo la historia y cualquier novedad que salga la estaré
reporting here on this channel, you already know that here I deal with all the entertainment topics from the heart
informando aquí en este canal ya sabéis que aquí trato todos los temas de la farándula del corazón
of the cotio YouTuber sauces also TV news Practically everything that is viral Like this
del cotio salseos de youtuber también noticias de la tele Prácticamente todo lo que sea viral Así
If you like and are interested in this content, it is very important that I realize that it is
que si te gusta y te interesa este contenido es muy importante que yo me dé cuenta como
mandatory to subscribe to the Channel, which is also completely free and you will not
suscribiéndote obligatorio suscríbete al Canal que además es completamente gratis y no te vas
regret it, friends of Didi like Drey, who was Rihana's best friend Until 2018 where
a arrepentir amigos de Didi como drey que fue el mejor amigo de rihana Hasta el año 2018 donde de
they suddenly stopped following each other is a person very close to Didi who has remained silent all this
repente se dejaron de seguir es una persona muy cercana a Didi ha guardado silencio todo este
time in the previous video I was giving you some examples, such as billion se
tiempo en el vídeo anterior os estuve poniendo algunos ejemplos Como por ejemplo de billon se
in which some probably do not talk about Didi and do not want to report things or
en la que probablemente algunos no hablen de Didi y no quieran denunciar las cosas o
speak out in respect and condemn him because they don't want doors to be closed or they are afraid of
pronunciarse al respeto y condenarlo porque no quieren que le cierren puertas o tienen miedo
commitment to friendships or simply that they have things to keep quiet about and they better keep quiet,
compromiso por amistades o simplemente que tienen cosas que callar y más les vales estarse quecito
I guess there is no need for introductions when we are talking about both Drake and the singer Milly
supongo que no hacen falta presentaciones cuando hablamos tanto de Drake como de la cantante Milly
Bobby Brown Although she is probably better known to many as Eleven, this girl, in
Bobby Brown Aunque seguramente para muchos es más conocidas como Eleven pero esta chica en
an interview when she was 14, talking about the friendship she had with Drake, commented that she spoke
una entrevista teniendo 14 años hablando sobre la amistad que mantenía con Drake comentó que hablaba
quite regularly with him on WhatsApp and that he was always telling her nice things.
de manera bastante habitual con él por WhatsApp y que este siempre le estaba diciendo cosas bonitas
It was like I missed her, saying good night, conversations, conversations, good friendship,
como que la extrañaba le daba las buenas noches conversaciones un conversaciones bueno amistad
a bit strange considering the age difference between the two of us, we're talking about
un tanto rara teniendo en cuenta la diferencia de edad que hay entre ambos estamos hablando de
a 31-year-old guy talking to a 14-year-old girl and maintaining this friendship and then she trying to
un tipo de 31 años hablando con una chica de 14 y manteniendo esta amistad y luego ella intentando
I imagine that clarifying so as not to leave things murky made it even worse by talking about how this
imagino que matizar para no dejar la cosa de turbia lo empeoró todavía más hablando de que este
Drake was advising her and giving her guidelines to follow with the boys. So you're going to tell me what a
Drake la aconsejaba y le daba pautas a seguir con los chicos O sea ya me dirás tú que pinta un tío
31-year-old guy looks like advising 14-year-old girls about How to act with the guys who want to flirt with her
de 31 palos aconsejando una niñas de 14 años sobre Cómo actuar con los chicos que se la quieren ligar
I understand that they were colleagues in the profession and that the other with more experience was
entiendo que fueran compañeros de la profesión y que el otro con más experiencia pues le estuviera
giving her advice about the union, not and giving professional advice but about men I don't know how you see it
dando consejos sobre el gremio no y dando consejos profesionales pero sobre hombres no sé cómo lo ve
miss you so much miss you more He's coming to Atlanta so
ustedes miss you so much miss you more He's coming to Atlanta so
I'm definitely going to go and see him What does he give you like What does he
I'm definitely going to go and see him What does he give you like What does he
say Drake responded to this at the time by asking the group not to interfere with his
say Drake respondió a esto en su momento pidiéndole a la peña que no se metieran entre sus
friends and he has a lot I'm lucky to have incredible people in my life. You can't choose that
amistades y él tengo mucha suerte de tener gente increíble en mi vida ustedes no pueden elegir eso
for me. It's good that people understand what I do. Now let's go back to talking about real problems
por mí es bueno que la gente entienda lo que yo hago ahora volvamos a hablar de problemas reales
in this world that aren't my friends. My God, I don't know what I want me to tell you. But Yes, it is true
en este mundo que no sean mis amistades Dios mío no sé qué queré que os diga Pero sí que es verdad
that a friendship between a guy with very black hair on his [__] and a minor to
que se ve un poco raro una amistad entre un tío con pelos en los [__] muy negros y una menor a
whom he is constantly saying that he misses her, Good night, pretty patatín patatán and giving her advice about boys seems a little strange
la que le está diciendo todo el tiempo que la extraña Buenas noches bonita patatín patatán y
. And how to be with them I don't know the truth is that this friendship seems a
dándole consejos sobre los chicos Y cómo estar con ellos no sé la verdad es que se me hace un
little strange to me. We can actually compare it with Henry Kavil who also met
poco raro est amistad la podemos comparar de hecho con Henry kavil que también conoció a
Miley during the filming of Nola Halmes and I tell you that we can compare it because Henry is true
Miley durante el rodaje de Nola halmes y os digo que la podemos comparar porque Henry sí que verdad
that she became quite friendly with Milly Bobby but putting a certain amount of ground in between, that is, due to
que cogió bastante amistad con Milly Bobby pero poniendo cierta tierra de por medio es decir por
the age difference between the two, it is true that he was evidently with her for
la diferencia de edad que había entre ambos sí que es verdad que evidentemente estuvo con ella para
everything that was necessary and to show her his support as a professional and as a partner. but basically
todo lo que hizo falta y para mostrarle su apoyo como profesional y como compañero pero básicamente
he gave her some guidelines apparently in which they did not enter into personal areas that
le puso unas pautas por lo visto en las que pues no entraban en terrenos personales que
were not appropriate between an adult and a minor. And we are talking about the fact that even though they had
no fueran adecuados entre un adulto y una menor Y eso que estamos hablando que ya aunque se llevaran
a years difference in age, we are talking about the fact that she was 18 Whether you want it or not,
años de diferencia de edad estamos hablando que ella tenía 18 que quieras que no sí que
it is true that she is still young but not small, like at 14, in that case everything was different, there are no
es verdad que sigue siendo joven pero no pequeña como con 14 en ese caso todo era diferente no hay
limits because it is as if we were all brothers, but with Henry he is very strict with me, which
límites porque es como si todos fuéramos hermanos pero con Henry él es muy estricto conmigo lo cual
I am grateful for. With Henry, he feels like a true adult relationship like a very good friendship a
agradezco con Henry se siente como una verdadera relación adulta como una muy buena amistad una
very healthy one that we have terms and conditions I know Henry he has terms and conditions
muy sana uno que tenemos términos y condiciones conozco a Henry él tiene términos y condiciones
with me I am not allowed to ask about his personal life he is like Milly Shut up no and I say something
conmigo no se me permite preguntar sobre su vida personal es como Milly Cállate no y yo digo algo
like understood I think you understand the difference between How Henry led friendship and How
como entendido creo que entendéis la diferencia entre Cómo llevó la amistad a Henry y Cómo la
Drake led it and that is more than obvious, it is something. For example, Didi's relationship with Justin Baver
lleva Drake y que es más que obvio es algo Como por ejemplo la relación de Didi con Justin baver
and what she did about having his guardianship for 48 hours, taking him to the party being a minor and having him
y aquello que hizo de tener su tutela por 48 horas llevárselo a la fiesta siendo menor y teniéndolo
there drinking By the way, I don't know if you remember that in any of these videos I was talking
allí bebiendo Por cierto no sé si recordaréis que en alguno de estos vídeos estuve hablando
about Billy English who, before being famous, was like a big fan of Justin Bieber and when he
de Billy english que en su día antes de ser famosa era como muy fan de Justin Bieber y este cuando la
met her he sponsored her in a certain way and was giving her advice about the career and
conoció como que la apadrinó de cierta forma y estuvo dándole consejos sobre la carrera y
so on so that things that had happened to him wouldn't happen to him it was like he protected her I don't want
demás para que no le pasaran cosas que la había sucedido a él era como que la protegió no quiero
her to lose him I don't want her to go through anything that I went through I wouldn't wish it on anyone
que ella perderlo no quiero que ella pase por nada de lo que yo pasé no se lo deseo a nadie
so yes yes some Maybe he needs me, I'm just a phone call away and it seems like Billy
así que si si alguna vez me necesita estoy a una llamada de distancia y al parecer sí que Billy
was safe, no, and he stayed distant from Didi. Although, however, there is a
estuvo como a salvo no y se mantuvo distante de Didi Aunque sin embargo sí que hay alguna
post on his Instagram in which he brags about having hugged Didi and puts those things in
publicación en su Instagram en la que al ardea de haber abrazado a Didi y pone esas cosas en
the comments No, here you have what he put on his Instagram account, I'll put it translated okay Although
los comentarios No aquí tenéis lo que puso en su cuenta de Instagram lo pongo traducido vale Aunque
Yes, I also have to tell you here that Billy recently made a reference to Didi and her
Sí también tengo que deciros aquí que Billy hace poco hizo una referencia a Didi y a sus fiestas
freff parties in case you haven't understood what he's saying It's something like that after the
freff por si no lo habéis entendido lo que viene a decir es algo así como que luego después del
concert there will be a party but it won't be a party. It's a joke. Let's say another one who apparently
concierto habrá una fiesta pero que no será una fiesta fre es una pullita digamos otra que al
was saved was Sabrina Carpenter, who in 2019 at the age of 19 was already a former Disney star.
parecer se salvó fue Sabrina Carpenter que en 2019 con 19 años siendo ya exestrella de Disney
at the beginning of his career he joked with Kesha's tiktok lyrics you already know the kesa
al comienzo de su carrera bromeaba con la letra de tiktok de Kesha ya sabéis la canción de kesa
tiktok song that now by the way he is changing it is rerecorded because he is completely
tiktok que ahora por cierto está cambiando la está regrabado porque está completamente en
against and deeply condemns what is happening with Didi and he very much regrets
contra y condena profundamente lo que está pasando con Didi y se arrepiente muchísimo
having that cameo in one of her most popular songs well well Sabrina Carpenter carpenter
de tener ese cameo en una de sus canciones más populares bien pues Sabrina Carpenter carpintero
because it is translated well well Sabrina in this tweet I woke up in the morning feeling like
porque está traducido bien pues Sabrina en este tweet me desperté por la mañana sintiéndome como
p Didi is a nod to the song he is mentioning that verse of that song but well let's hope
p Didi es un guiño a la canción está mencionando esa estrofa de esa canción pero bueno esperemos
that finally not has never attended any of those parties, I think that no other person who tried
que finalmente no haya acudido nunca a alguna de esas fiestas creo que no otra persona que procuró
to stay away from was Selena Gómez, I think that Justin Bieber's best-known partner, even
mantenerse lejos de fue Selena Gómez creo que la pareja más conocida de Justin Bieber incluso que
the one he has today, was Justin Bieber's girlfriend in 2011, in fact. There is even talk
la que tiene a día de hoy fue novia de Justin Bieber en el año 2011 de hecho Incluso se habla
that she herself tried to keep Justin away from Didi, even though she didn't succeed very well, and
de que ella misma intentó alejar a Justin de Didi también aunque no lo lograse mucho y Didi
when Didi met her at a party, she pretended to confuse her with the one who parked the cars.
cuando se la encontró en una fiesta hizo como que la confundía con la que aparcaba los coches
Look, I see everything, I don't care. In fact, I laughed. hysterically when it happened but I
mira lo veo todo no me importa De hecho me reí histéricamente cuando sucedió pero lo
understand it I know what it's all about in one of Selena Gómez's songs I put it
entiendo sé de qué se trata todo en una de las canciones de Selena Gómez os Lo pongo
here on the screen so as not to pronounce it I'm okay And I don't have much of my pronunciation
aquí en pantalla para no pronunciarlo yo vale Y que no r mucho de mi pronunciación
but practically there are many people who think that Selena does Surely she
pero prácticamente hay mucha gente que piensa que Selena sí que seguramente se
was involved in one of this party and that this video clip is some
vio envuelta en alguna de esta fiesta y que esto del videoclip es alguna
reference, it could have absolutely nothing to do with it. And it could be a video clip that has absolutely no
referencia podría no tener absolutamente nada que Y ser un videoclip que no tiene absolutamente
reference to the padad party but you already know that these people are very into doing this
ningún guiño hacia la fiesta de padad pero ya sabéis que esta gente son muy de hacer este
type of very direct, non-indirect references in his video clips. Even in the lyrics of his
tipo de referencias no indirectas muy directas en sus videoclips Incluso en las letras de sus
songs, it is common for Justin Bieber. Even I believe that over the years we will
canciones es habitual en Justin Bieber incluso yo creo que durante el paso de los años iremos
discover even more subliminal messages that Justin would have left in one of his video clips and
descubriendo todavía más mensajes subliminales que Justin habría dejado en alguno de sus videoclips y
well, although supposedly If she had this tension with Didi, it is true that she has been seen,
bueno aunque supuestamente tuviese esta tirantez con Didi sí que es verdad que se le ha visto
although not at the parties as such, involved in some after-events such as the NTTV that you already
aunque no en las fiestas como tal involucrada en alguna after de eventos como los ntv que ya
know were also sponsored by Didi. Here you have the same image from 2023, that is,
sabéis que también estaban auspiciados por Didi aquí tenéis una imagen misma del 2023 o sea hace
not long ago. At this point the truth is that I have my doubts and I don't like it at all and it seems [__]
nada llegado a este punto la verdad es que tengo mis dudas y no me gusta nada y se me hace [__]
I hope I'm wrong but the clip is with naa the little friend of Didi's little daughters who in
ojalá me equivoque pero el clip este con naa la amiguita de las hijas pequeñas de Didi que en
this clip that I'm going to show you Next, he tells a little bit about how he met her and why she
este clip que os voy a poner a continuación cuenta un poco Cómo la conoció Y por qué lo
calls him papa cams. Well, I don't know if the real version would be this, but the truth is that I don't like it.
llama papá cams Pues no sé yo si la versión real sería esta pero la verdad es que no me gusta
Well, did's modus operandi used to be when someone liked him. Well, let's see when I say he
en fin el modus operandi de did solía ser cuando le gustaba a alguien bueno a ver cuando digo le
liked it, I mean like a talent house, okay, let's say that to the kids, the children
gustaba me refiero en plan casa talento vale vamos a decir eso a los chavales a los niños
or young people, he promised them the world as a flag, as they say, no. In other words, he promised them a promising future
o jóvenes les prometía el mundo por bandera como se dice no O sea les prometía un futuro
in the world of stardom, this included taking them to big events. already big parties
prometedor en el mundo del estrellato esto incluía llevarlos a grandes eventos y a grandes fiestas
and according to what is mentioned in this latest complaint that he used to drug people sometimes
y según se Comenta en esta última denuncia que le han puesto solía drogar losos algunas veces
by putting things in their drinks without them realizing this is a tremendous accusation okay but it is
metiéndole cosas en las bebidas sin que se dieran cuenta esto es tremenda acusación vale pero es
what he is being accused of because then they suddenly woke up with Didi in the bed
de lo que se le está acusando de que luego de repente despertaban con Didi en la cama
in the press was that When when you were handed a drink and Now We know that the drink is la was
in the press was that When when you were handed a drink and Now We know that the drink is la was
something if you refuse to drink it You were kicked out of the party Let that sink in for
something if you refuse to drink it You were kicked out of the party Let that sink in for
a minute I mean the admission To This Party was that you Had to drink this the chosen drink that
a minute i mean the admission To This Party was that you Had to drink this the chosen drink that
was handed to you Uh and Now We know that in most cases I would say 9% of the cases Uh
was handed to you Uh and Now We know that that in in most cases I would say 9% of the cases Uh
these individuals were drugged with some sort of drug That's that was kind of the mo another
these individuals were drugged with some sort of drug That's that was kind of the mo another
instance this individual Who was 9 years old at the time Uh was taken to an audition in New
instance this individual Who was n9 years old at the time Uh was taken to a audition in New
York City with Bad Boy Records Uh other Boys were there to audition as well All of them were
York City with Bad Boy Records Uh other Boys were there to audition as well All of them were
trying to Land a record deal All of them were miners Uh this individual was sexually abused
trying to Land a record deal All of them were miners Uh this individual was sexually abused
allegedly by Sean comes and several other people at the Studio Uh prom his parents
allegedly by sean comes and several other people at the Studio Uh prom his parents
and
and
de By that he would make him aar but he needed a visit with him in private about it
de By that he would make him aar but he needed a visit with him in private about it
away from Uh his parents once Uh they were in a private area allegedly mres made the victim
away from Uh his parents once Uh they were in a private Area allegedly mres made the victim
Upon him another incident an individual 15 years old at the time flown to New York City to attend
Upon him another incident an individual 15 years old at the time flown to New York City to attend
a Party Uh Was drugged and then taken into a private room allegedly in the presence of Mr
a Party Uh Was drugged and then taken into a private room allegedly in the presence of Mr
comes Uh Where this Uh female individual Minor and then other indiv tooks ind 2
comes Uh Where this Uh female individual Minor and then other indiv tooks ind 2
the time of the occurrence Uh was picked up by allegedly by Mr comes and several other
the time of the occurrence Uh was picked up by allegedly by Mr comes and several other
people Uh in a Black suv from the airport Uh was given One drink in the suv and then
people Uh in a Black suv from the airport Uh was given One drink in the suv and then
literally woke up the next day not knowing What Had happened but with Pain and damage to both
literally woke up the next day not knowing What Had happened but with Pain and damage to both
her She then went to the hospital She was missing her underwear and her Shoes
her She then went to the hospital She was missing her underwear and her Shoes
another instance individual Uh this Time not a Minor Uh was attended a Group dinner allegedly
another instance individual Uh this Time not a Minor Uh was attended a Group dinner allegedly
with Sean Combes in Miami Uh She wasn't drinking Because She was pregnant Uh but She Whatever
with sean combes in Miami Uh She wasn't drinking Because She was pregnant Uh but She Whatever
She drank at the table apparently at least according to her was laced with something She
She drank at the table apparently at least according to her was laced with something She
blacked out and She woke up In The same Bed Again allegedly with Mr hes And I could go on I mean
blacked out and She woke Up In The same Bed Again allegedly with Mr hes And I could go on I mean
in fact some things are so delicate things that I can't even mention here because
de hecho algunas cosas son tan delicadas que no puedo ni mencionar aquí porque
YouTube gets silly, but people who arrived with wounds on their parts where
YouTube se pone tonto pero gente que llegaba con heridas en su partes donde
they shouldn't have wounds and signs of being drugged with horse medicine
no deberían tener heridas y signos de ser drogados con medicina para caballo
, that is, we are talking about very strong things, not in this complaint
o sea estamos hablando de cosas muy fuertes no en esta denuncia
old at the time Uh was asked to attend Just Saw on the street asked to attend a Party
old at the time Uh was asked to attend Just Saw on the street asked to attend a Party
in a hotel um She was flattered went to the party was given One drink and doesn't remember
in a hotel um She was flattered went to the party was given One drink and doesn't remember
anything Else ultimately Uh was so messed up was went to the hospital Where they found um
anything Else ultimately Uh was so messed up was went to the hospital Where they found um
cocaine and this horse tranquilizer in her Blood System Had he not been
cocaine and this horse tranquilizer in her Blood System Had he not been
also highlighting one thing that I was telling you in the previous video but in case
destacar también una cosa que os estuve diciendo en el vídeo anterior pero por si
you haven't seen it, there were more than 3000 people who contacted this
no lo habéis visto fueron más de 3000 personas las que se contactaron con este buffet de este
man 's buffet that you are looking at and they chose the 120 cases trying to Well summarize the
señor que estáis viendo y eligieron los 120 casos intentando Bueno resumir un poco la
situation a little not to avoid having 3000 cases going to the clearest ones okay going to the
situación no para no tener 3000 casos yendo a los más claros vale yendo los
most powerful ones now I don't know if you agree with me that I understand that practically no one
más potentes ahora no sé si estáis de acuerdo conmigo en que comprendo que prácticamente pas
is with all their money and with all his means trying to get an agreement in which
esté con todo su dinero y con todos sus medios intentando conseguir un acuerdo en el que lo
they put him on conditional release and blah blah blah and he doesn't get it, I honestly think that he has a
ponen en libertad condicional y bla bla bla y no lo consiga creo que sinceramente lo tiene
very difficult time on this occasion. In fact, I think that not only should he fall, but
muy complicado en esta ocasión de hecho creo que no debería solamente caer él sino que se
they should also find out who They have been Accomplices because he has not been able to do this alone Selma Fonseca,
averigüe también Quiénes han sido Cómplices porque esto no lo ha podido hacer él solo Selma Fonseca
Didi's photographer. During the last 20 years she said that at all of Didi's parties
la fotógrafa de Didi Durante los últimos 20 años dijo que en todas las fiestas de Didi
she saw minors and that she also has thousands of photos where it can be verified sadly despite
vio a menores y que además tiene miles de fotos donde se puede comprobar lastimosamente a pesar
being published on her page, some of them are very sensitive to the fact that no one
de estar publicadas en su página algunas de ellas está muy delicada con Que nadie
publishes them without agreeing on remuneration, that is, I don't know, the truth is that I see her a little strange.
las publique sin acordar una remuneración o sea está no sé la verdad es que la veo un poco rara
I don't understand if she wants to collaborate or rather wants to take advantage of the situation, in fact. Well,
No entiendo si quiere colaborar o más bien quiere aprovecharse de la situación de hecho Bueno por
here I am going to be putting some Although they are going to be a little blurred, that is, the editor is going
aquí voy a estar poniendo algunas Aunque van a estar un poco blur adas o sea el editor lo va
to blur them a little, it is going to differentiate more or less the photos and They are as they are, no
a blur rear un poco se va a diferenciar no que más o menos la fotos y Son como son no
, but since it is a little delicate with the subject copyright, I see her capable of claiming
pero como está un poquito delicada con el tema de copyright demás la veo capaz de reclamarnos
the video from us, so well, here you have the website. Look here, the editor will be putting
el vídeo así que bueno por ahí tenéis la página web Mira por aquí os estará poniendo el editor el
the link for you so that you can go see her website, but let's see, you can clearly differentiate
el link vale para que vayáis a ver la su página web pero vamos se pueden diferenciar perfectamente
that there are people here. that they are not of legal age or a joke, the Mexican singer
que aquí hay personas que no son mayores de edad ni de coña también ha salido la cantante mexicana
Elan has also come out, who was in the world of music at the beginning of the 2000s and all these parties. She says
elan que estuvo a principios de los años 2000 en el mundo de la música y todas estas fiestas Dice
that as such she never attended a Didi party but pay attention some party of Leonardo
que como tal no llegó asistir nunca a una fiesta de Didi pero sí atentos alguna fiesta de Leonardo
DiCaprio Leonardo DiCaprio is coming out quite splashed in this investigation and it does not surprise me
DiCaprio Leonardo DiCaprio está saliendo bastante salpicado en esta investigación y no me extraña
that he was saving this clip the controversial topic of next year of 2025 2026 that is, he has
que fuese guardar este clip el tema controversial del año que viene del del 2025 2026 o sea tiene
too many strange things this man we have already been seeing throughout the videos that we have been
demasiado cosas raras este hombre ya hemos estado viendo a lo largo de los vídeos que hemos estado
covering in this series as we have caught images of him smelling the hair of young girls and all this
tratando en esta serie como hemos pillado imágenes de él oliéndole el pelo a jovencitas y todo esto
talk about him that every time a girlfriend turns 25 he leaves her fortunately never but
que se habla de él de que cada vez que una novia cumple 25 la deja afortunadamente de él nunca pero
I do want to tell you one thing The music industry has always been this thing of
sí les quiero decir una cosa la industria de la música eh siempre ha sido esta cosa de de
connections and parties and meetings has been the type of person who, if he arrives at a place and feels
conexiones y de fiestas y de reuniones ha sido el tipo de persona que si llega a un lugar y siente
a negative or heavy vibe, I leave, I leave at that moment, I don't have to stay there
una vibra negativa o pesada me voy me largo en ese instante no tengo por qué quedarme ahí
to see if things get worse, in fact, yes, I had several parties at his house but I go back
a ver si la cosa ponen peor de hecho sí de este me tocaron varias fiestas en su casa pero vuelvo
to the same thing, that is, on the day you arrive, everything is fine, everything is normal, the people seem normal. This is kind of like
a lo mismo o sea en el día llegas todo bien todo normal la gente parece normal Este un po como una
something like zombies or like vampires, the sun goes down, things get a little strange. and you leave
cosa como como de zombies o como vampiro baja el sol la cosa se pone un poquito extraña y te largas
well that's what I really did Hollywood is full of sharks and [__] so elitos for
bueno eso hacía yo de verdad Hollywood está lleno de tiburones y de [__] entonces de elitos para
me has always been better some have commented like with the other video that I uploaded saying that
mí siempre ha sido mejor algunos han comentado tipo con el otro video que subí diciendo que
I had been at Leonardo Decapro's house for certain parties saying that I was leaving early and
había estado en casa de de Leonardo decapro para ciertas fiestas diciendo que me iba temprano y
everyone said no and of course everyone says they are leaving early to see I'm not everyone's
todos así de no y es que claro todo el mundo dice que se va temprano a ver yo no soy todo el mundo
number one no no I'm not trying to convince I mean I don't have a heavy conscience I know I don't live there anymore
número uno no no no estoy tratando de convencer o sea yo no tengo la conciencia pesada Yo sé que ya
, I'm not there and I know why I'm not there and it's because I didn't like that life and this
no vivo ahí no estoy ahí y yo sé por qué no estoy ahí y es porque a mí no me gustaba esa vida y este
and thank God it never got older so that I would say gee I have to escape from this so
y gracias a Dios nunca pasó a mayores para que yo dijera geey me tengo que escapar de esto entonces
I have the conscience completely Clear and I continue to say the same thing there are more than those who believe there are
tengo la conciencia completamente Clara y sigo diciendo lo mismo hay más de los que creen son
many more just while I am recording This video Juanito has published this tweet the
muchísimos más justo mientras que estoy grabando Este vídeo Juanito ha publicado este tweet la
night when no one believed brne peer in 2007 while they were celebrating the birthday of Casandra
noche en la que nadie creyó a brne peer en 2007 mientras celebraban el cumpleaños de Casandra
Ventura ex-partner of Didi sa casasi had to carry Britney Spear out and the press assumed
Ventura expareja de Didi sa casasi tuvieron que sacar en brazos a Britney Spear y la prensa asumió
it was because she was an alcoholic. To this day she claims that someone drugged her by putting
que se debe a que ella era alcohólica hasta el día de hoy ella afirma que alguien la drog poniéndole
something in her drink. Among the guests were Dallas at Paris Hilton and obviously Cindy. camps
algo en su bebida entre los invitados estaban Dallas atin Paris Hilton y obviamente Cindy camps
now what do you think family now that we have everything we have on the table How things are
ahora qué pensáis familia ahora que tenemos sobre la mesa todo lo que tenemos Cómo son las cosas e
many times and how time puts them in their place eh not a eh measly trace of this
muchas veces y como el tiempo las va poniendo en su sitio eh ni un eh mísero rastro de esta
Britney And you will say Well it's been a long time there are 6 years of difference between one pressure and the
Britney Y ustedes dirán Bueno pasó mucho tiempo hay 6 años de diferencia entre una presión y la
other it turns out that the night before Guess who she had gone out to party with who
otra resulta que la noche anterior Adivinen con quién había salido de fiesta quién la
had taken her to party with Brindy Spears just the night before this BM presentation
había llevado de fiesta a brindy Spears justo la noche antes de esta presentación de las BM
you don't have to guess much John did coms alias pd There are photos that prove it and it seems that PD
no tienen que adivinar mucho John did coms alias pd hay fotos que lo prueban y Parece ser que pd
has already been accused by other female artists of having been drugged to then fulfill certain
ya ha sido acusado por otras mujeres artistas de haber sido drogadas para luego cumplir con ciertos
certain fantasies that the artist had bar rapper bar producer at the moment we are going to leave today's video
ciertas fantasías que tenía el artista bar rapero barra productor de momento el vídeo
here but You already know that I am at the bottom of the news, I have to dedicate
de hoy lo vamos a dejar por aquí pero ya sabéis que estoy al pie de la noticia tengo que dedicar
the day and I have to dedicate a couple of videos to a series of things so I don't know if the next video
el día y tengo que dedicar un par de vídeos a una serie de cosas así que no sé si el próximo vídeo
is going to be on this topic or maybe later in the week we will come back Let's see each other But that's why
va a ser sobre este tema o tal vez más adelante durante la semana volvamos a vernos Pero por eso
it's very important that you subscribe to the Channel, follow me on Twitter, follow me on Instagram because
es muy importante que os suscribáis al Canal me sigáis en Twitter me sigáis en instagram porque
there I will be very active, keeping you informed of everything that comes out and when I release
por ahí estaré muy activo manteniendo informado de cada cosa que vaya saliendo y de cuándo saco
a family video. A huge kiss, I love you very much. Thank you for the support that you are giving to the
vídeo familia Un beso enorme os quiero muchísimo Gracias por el apoyo que le estáis dando a los
channels, also remind you that apart from Twitter Instagram there is the salsería where I talk about
canales recordaros también que aparte de Twitter Instagram está la salsería donde hablo de salsos
YouTube salsas and telesalseo where I talk about the gossip press and Spanish TV bye guapos
de youtub y telesalseo donde hablo de la prensa del corazón y de la tele española chao guapos